What I call bricks without straw features to them
on bricks Without Straw projects. And I'm sure you've all experienced this. I'd be astounded if you haven't
So one project that I worked on
It was about 100 people. It was government project. It was kind of automate an ancient process. Kind of turn the whole thing, digitize the whole process.
And
So there was lots and lots of work going on which made it kind of a stretch. It was going to be difficult because it was attempting to digitize this process from beginning to end that had been run on paper for kind of hundreds and hundreds of years. So that was a stretch
But kind of
The extra bet that they'd kind of like laid on top of that, amongst others was that this could be done
With terrible
Internet connections, just like kind of with
appalling connections to the Internet. At one point, one of the people that I was working with when we were trying to raise this problem
said
In order to make internets, you need internets.
kind of having to explain to somebody that that's actually what you need to do.